the [ __ ] frog dude It's not that the first
la rana tío No es que la primera
time Dallas spoke to me on
vez que a mí el Dallas me habló por
WhatsApp he asked uncle shur for my phone number
WhatsApp que le pidió mi teléfono al tío
in 2019 and uncle sh gave it to him and he
shur en 2019 y el tío sh se lo dio y me
spoke to me on WhatsApp and this who the [ __ ] is he
habló por WhatsApp y este quién es
with a frog and it was the D he didn't have the frog he
con una rana y era el D no tenía la rana
never changed the frog I mean
ya la rana no la ha cambiado nunca O sea
look at the number of years I've been
fijaros la cantidad de años que os estoy
talking to you I'm used to that
hablando yo estoy acostumbrado a que
when I look at my phone from afar I see how
cuando veo el móvil de lejos veo lo
green that Dallas is and now
verde ese que es el Dallas y ahora de
suddenly I see all of Twitter that you
repente me veo a todo Twitter que te
go into and it's with the frog I mean I see
metes y está con la rana O sea me veo a
all of Twitter with the green with the green
todo Twitter con el verde con el verde
look here you see it all green look everything
mira aquí lo veis todo verde mira todo
full of frog I see it now
lleno de rana me lo veo ahora está ya
the frog thing is calmer now it's a
más tranquilita la cosa de la rana ya
little more relaxed No yes things are more relaxed
un poco No sí está más relajado la cosa
but yesterday it was all the notifications
pero ayer era todas las notificaciones
Frog Frog Frog frog the frog What's up
Rana Rana Rana rana la ranera Qué pasa
my tern What's up my tern
mi charran ería Qué pasa mi charran ería
all of Twitter with the frog and it's that it's
todo Twitter con la rana y es que es la
people putting the profile picture
gente poniéndose la foto de perfil
because they found it funny seeing
porque le han hecho gracia vérselas al
Dallas
Dallas